[
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of bulbasaur?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of bulbasaur is 1"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ivysaur?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ivysaur is 2"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of venusaur?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of venusaur is 3"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of charmander?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of charmander is 4"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of charmeleon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of charmeleon is 5"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of charizard?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of charizard is 6"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of squirtle?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of squirtle is 7"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of wartortle?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of wartortle is 8"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of blastoise?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of blastoise is 9"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of caterpie?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of caterpie is 10"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of metapod?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of metapod is 11"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of butterfree?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of butterfree is 12"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of weedle?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of weedle is 13"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of kakuna?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of kakuna is 14"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of beedrill?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of beedrill is 15"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of pidgey?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of pidgey is 16"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of pidgeotto?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of pidgeotto is 17"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of pidgeot?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of pidgeot is 18"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of rattata?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of rattata is 19"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of raticate?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of raticate is 20"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of spearow?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of spearow is 21"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of fearow?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of fearow is 22"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ekans?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ekans is 23"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of arbok?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of arbok is 24"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of pikachu?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of pikachu is 25"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of raichu?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of raichu is 26"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of sandshrew?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of sandshrew is 27"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of sandslash?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of sandslash is 28"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of nidoran-f?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of nidoran-f is 29"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of nidorina?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of nidorina is 30"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of nidoqueen?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of nidoqueen is 31"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of nidoran-m?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of nidoran-m is 32"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of nidorino?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of nidorino is 33"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of nidoking?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of nidoking is 34"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of clefairy?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of clefairy is 35"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of clefable?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of clefable is 36"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of vulpix?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of vulpix is 37"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ninetales?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ninetales is 38"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of jigglypuff?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of jigglypuff is 39"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of wigglytuff?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of wigglytuff is 40"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of zubat?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of zubat is 41"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of golbat?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of golbat is 42"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of oddish?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of oddish is 43"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gloom?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gloom is 44"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of vileplume?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of vileplume is 45"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of paras?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of paras is 46"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of parasect?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of parasect is 47"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of venonat?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of venonat is 48"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of venomoth?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of venomoth is 49"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of diglett?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of diglett is 50"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of dugtrio?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of dugtrio is 51"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of meowth?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of meowth is 52"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of persian?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of persian is 53"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of psyduck?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of psyduck is 54"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of golduck?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of golduck is 55"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mankey?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mankey is 56"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of primeape?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of primeape is 57"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of growlithe?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of growlithe is 58"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of arcanine?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of arcanine is 59"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of poliwag?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of poliwag is 60"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of poliwhirl?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of poliwhirl is 61"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of poliwrath?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of poliwrath is 62"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of abra?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of abra is 63"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of kadabra?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of kadabra is 64"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of alakazam?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of alakazam is 65"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of machop?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of machop is 66"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of machoke?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of machoke is 67"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of machamp?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of machamp is 68"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of bellsprout?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of bellsprout is 69"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of weepinbell?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of weepinbell is 70"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of victreebel?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of victreebel is 71"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of tentacool?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of tentacool is 72"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of tentacruel?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of tentacruel is 73"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of geodude?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of geodude is 74"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of graveler?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of graveler is 75"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of golem?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of golem is 76"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ponyta?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ponyta is 77"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of rapidash?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of rapidash is 78"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of slowpoke?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of slowpoke is 79"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of slowbro?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of slowbro is 80"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of magnemite?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of magnemite is 81"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of magneton?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of magneton is 82"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of farfetchd?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of farfetchd is 83"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of doduo?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of doduo is 84"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of dodrio?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of dodrio is 85"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of seel?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of seel is 86"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of dewgong?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of dewgong is 87"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of grimer?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of grimer is 88"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of muk?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of muk is 89"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of shellder?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of shellder is 90"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of cloyster?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of cloyster is 91"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gastly?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gastly is 92"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of haunter?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of haunter is 93"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gengar?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gengar is 94"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of onix?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of onix is 95"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of drowzee?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of drowzee is 96"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of hypno?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of hypno is 97"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of krabby?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of krabby is 98"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of kingler?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of kingler is 99"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of voltorb?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of voltorb is 100"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of electrode?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of electrode is 101"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of exeggcute?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of exeggcute is 102"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of exeggutor?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of exeggutor is 103"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of cubone?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of cubone is 104"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of marowak?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of marowak is 105"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of hitmonlee?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of hitmonlee is 106"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of hitmonchan?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of hitmonchan is 107"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lickitung?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lickitung is 108"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of koffing?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of koffing is 109"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of weezing?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of weezing is 110"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of rhyhorn?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of rhyhorn is 111"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of rhydon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of rhydon is 112"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of chansey?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of chansey is 113"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of tangela?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of tangela is 114"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of kangaskhan?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of kangaskhan is 115"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of horsea?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of horsea is 116"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of seadra?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of seadra is 117"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of goldeen?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of goldeen is 118"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of seaking?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of seaking is 119"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of staryu?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of staryu is 120"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of starmie?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of starmie is 121"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mr-mime?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mr-mime is 122"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of scyther?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of scyther is 123"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of jynx?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of jynx is 124"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of electabuzz?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of electabuzz is 125"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of magmar?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of magmar is 126"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of pinsir?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of pinsir is 127"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of tauros?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of tauros is 128"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of magikarp?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of magikarp is 129"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gyarados?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gyarados is 130"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lapras?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lapras is 131"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ditto?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ditto is 132"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of eevee?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of eevee is 133"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of vaporeon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of vaporeon is 134"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of jolteon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of jolteon is 135"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of flareon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of flareon is 136"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of porygon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of porygon is 137"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of omanyte?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of omanyte is 138"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of omastar?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of omastar is 139"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of kabuto?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of kabuto is 140"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of kabutops?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of kabutops is 141"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of aerodactyl?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of aerodactyl is 142"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of snorlax?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of snorlax is 143"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of articuno?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of articuno is 144"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of zapdos?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of zapdos is 145"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of moltres?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of moltres is 146"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of dratini?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of dratini is 147"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of dragonair?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of dragonair is 148"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of dragonite?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of dragonite is 149"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mewtwo?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mewtwo is 150"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mew?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mew is 151"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of chikorita?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of chikorita is 152"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of bayleef?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of bayleef is 153"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of meganium?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of meganium is 154"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of cyndaquil?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of cyndaquil is 155"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of quilava?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of quilava is 156"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of typhlosion?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of typhlosion is 157"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of totodile?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of totodile is 158"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of croconaw?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of croconaw is 159"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of feraligatr?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of feraligatr is 160"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of sentret?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of sentret is 161"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of furret?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of furret is 162"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of hoothoot?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of hoothoot is 163"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of noctowl?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of noctowl is 164"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ledyba?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ledyba is 165"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ledian?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ledian is 166"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of spinarak?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of spinarak is 167"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ariados?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ariados is 168"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of crobat?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of crobat is 169"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of chinchou?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of chinchou is 170"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lanturn?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lanturn is 171"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of pichu?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of pichu is 172"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of cleffa?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of cleffa is 173"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of igglybuff?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of igglybuff is 174"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of togepi?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of togepi is 175"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of togetic?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of togetic is 176"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of natu?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of natu is 177"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of xatu?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of xatu is 178"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mareep?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mareep is 179"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of flaaffy?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of flaaffy is 180"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ampharos?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ampharos is 181"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of bellossom?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of bellossom is 182"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of marill?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of marill is 183"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of azumarill?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of azumarill is 184"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of sudowoodo?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of sudowoodo is 185"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of politoed?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of politoed is 186"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of hoppip?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of hoppip is 187"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of skiploom?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of skiploom is 188"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of jumpluff?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of jumpluff is 189"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of aipom?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of aipom is 190"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of sunkern?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of sunkern is 191"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of sunflora?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of sunflora is 192"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of yanma?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of yanma is 193"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of wooper?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of wooper is 194"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of quagsire?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of quagsire is 195"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of espeon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of espeon is 196"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of umbreon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of umbreon is 197"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of murkrow?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of murkrow is 198"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of slowking?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of slowking is 199"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of misdreavus?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of misdreavus is 200"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of unown?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of unown is 201"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of wobbuffet?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of wobbuffet is 202"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of girafarig?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of girafarig is 203"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of pineco?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of pineco is 204"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of forretress?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of forretress is 205"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of dunsparce?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of dunsparce is 206"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gligar?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gligar is 207"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of steelix?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of steelix is 208"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of snubbull?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of snubbull is 209"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of granbull?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of granbull is 210"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of qwilfish?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of qwilfish is 211"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of scizor?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of scizor is 212"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of shuckle?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of shuckle is 213"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of heracross?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of heracross is 214"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of sneasel?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of sneasel is 215"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of teddiursa?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of teddiursa is 216"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ursaring?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ursaring is 217"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of slugma?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of slugma is 218"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of magcargo?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of magcargo is 219"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of swinub?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of swinub is 220"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of piloswine?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of piloswine is 221"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of corsola?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of corsola is 222"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of remoraid?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of remoraid is 223"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of octillery?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of octillery is 224"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of delibird?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of delibird is 225"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mantine?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mantine is 226"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of skarmory?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of skarmory is 227"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of houndour?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of houndour is 228"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of houndoom?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of houndoom is 229"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of kingdra?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of kingdra is 230"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of phanpy?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of phanpy is 231"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of donphan?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of donphan is 232"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of porygon2?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of porygon2 is 233"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of stantler?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of stantler is 234"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of smeargle?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of smeargle is 235"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of tyrogue?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of tyrogue is 236"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of hitmontop?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of hitmontop is 237"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of smoochum?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of smoochum is 238"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of elekid?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of elekid is 239"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of magby?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of magby is 240"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of miltank?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of miltank is 241"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of blissey?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of blissey is 242"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of raikou?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of raikou is 243"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of entei?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of entei is 244"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of suicune?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of suicune is 245"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of larvitar?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of larvitar is 246"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of pupitar?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of pupitar is 247"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of tyranitar?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of tyranitar is 248"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lugia?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lugia is 249"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ho-oh?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ho-oh is 250"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of celebi?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of celebi is 251"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of treecko?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of treecko is 252"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of grovyle?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of grovyle is 253"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of sceptile?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of sceptile is 254"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of torchic?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of torchic is 255"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of combusken?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of combusken is 256"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of blaziken?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of blaziken is 257"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mudkip?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mudkip is 258"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of marshtomp?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of marshtomp is 259"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of swampert?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of swampert is 260"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of poochyena?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of poochyena is 261"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mightyena?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mightyena is 262"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of zigzagoon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of zigzagoon is 263"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of linoone?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of linoone is 264"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of wurmple?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of wurmple is 265"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of silcoon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of silcoon is 266"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of beautifly?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of beautifly is 267"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of cascoon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of cascoon is 268"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of dustox?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of dustox is 269"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lotad?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lotad is 270"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lombre?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lombre is 271"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ludicolo?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ludicolo is 272"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of seedot?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of seedot is 273"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of nuzleaf?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of nuzleaf is 274"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of shiftry?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of shiftry is 275"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of taillow?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of taillow is 276"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of swellow?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of swellow is 277"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of wingull?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of wingull is 278"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of pelipper?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of pelipper is 279"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ralts?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ralts is 280"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of kirlia?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of kirlia is 281"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gardevoir?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gardevoir is 282"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of surskit?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of surskit is 283"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of masquerain?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of masquerain is 284"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of shroomish?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of shroomish is 285"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of breloom?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of breloom is 286"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of slakoth?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of slakoth is 287"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of vigoroth?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of vigoroth is 288"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of slaking?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of slaking is 289"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of nincada?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of nincada is 290"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ninjask?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ninjask is 291"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of shedinja?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of shedinja is 292"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of whismur?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of whismur is 293"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of loudred?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of loudred is 294"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of exploud?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of exploud is 295"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of makuhita?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of makuhita is 296"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of hariyama?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of hariyama is 297"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of azurill?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of azurill is 298"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of nosepass?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of nosepass is 299"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of skitty?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of skitty is 300"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of delcatty?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of delcatty is 301"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of sableye?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of sableye is 302"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mawile?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mawile is 303"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of aron?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of aron is 304"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lairon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lairon is 305"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of aggron?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of aggron is 306"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of meditite?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of meditite is 307"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of medicham?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of medicham is 308"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of electrike?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of electrike is 309"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of manectric?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of manectric is 310"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of plusle?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of plusle is 311"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of minun?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of minun is 312"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of volbeat?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of volbeat is 313"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of illumise?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of illumise is 314"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of roselia?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of roselia is 315"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gulpin?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gulpin is 316"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of swalot?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of swalot is 317"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of carvanha?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of carvanha is 318"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of sharpedo?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of sharpedo is 319"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of wailmer?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of wailmer is 320"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of wailord?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of wailord is 321"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of numel?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of numel is 322"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of camerupt?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of camerupt is 323"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of torkoal?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of torkoal is 324"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of spoink?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of spoink is 325"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of grumpig?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of grumpig is 326"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of spinda?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of spinda is 327"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of trapinch?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of trapinch is 328"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of vibrava?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of vibrava is 329"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of flygon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of flygon is 330"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of cacnea?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of cacnea is 331"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of cacturne?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of cacturne is 332"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of swablu?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of swablu is 333"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of altaria?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of altaria is 334"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of zangoose?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of zangoose is 335"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of seviper?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of seviper is 336"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lunatone?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lunatone is 337"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of solrock?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of solrock is 338"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of barboach?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of barboach is 339"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of whiscash?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of whiscash is 340"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of corphish?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of corphish is 341"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of crawdaunt?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of crawdaunt is 342"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of baltoy?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of baltoy is 343"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of claydol?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of claydol is 344"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lileep?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lileep is 345"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of cradily?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of cradily is 346"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of anorith?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of anorith is 347"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of armaldo?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of armaldo is 348"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of feebas?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of feebas is 349"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of milotic?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of milotic is 350"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of castform?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of castform is 351"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of kecleon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of kecleon is 352"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of shuppet?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of shuppet is 353"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of banette?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of banette is 354"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of duskull?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of duskull is 355"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of dusclops?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of dusclops is 356"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of tropius?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of tropius is 357"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of chimecho?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of chimecho is 358"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of absol?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of absol is 359"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of wynaut?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of wynaut is 360"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of snorunt?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of snorunt is 361"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of glalie?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of glalie is 362"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of spheal?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of spheal is 363"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of sealeo?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of sealeo is 364"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of walrein?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of walrein is 365"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of clamperl?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of clamperl is 366"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of huntail?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of huntail is 367"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gorebyss?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gorebyss is 368"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of relicanth?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of relicanth is 369"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of luvdisc?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of luvdisc is 370"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of bagon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of bagon is 371"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of shelgon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of shelgon is 372"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of salamence?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of salamence is 373"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of beldum?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of beldum is 374"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of metang?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of metang is 375"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of metagross?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of metagross is 376"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of regirock?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of regirock is 377"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of regice?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of regice is 378"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of registeel?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of registeel is 379"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of latias?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of latias is 380"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of latios?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of latios is 381"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of kyogre?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of kyogre is 382"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of groudon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of groudon is 383"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of rayquaza?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of rayquaza is 384"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of jirachi?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of jirachi is 385"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of deoxys-normal?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of deoxys-normal is 386"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of turtwig?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of turtwig is 387"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of grotle?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of grotle is 388"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of torterra?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of torterra is 389"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of chimchar?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of chimchar is 390"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of monferno?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of monferno is 391"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of infernape?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of infernape is 392"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of piplup?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of piplup is 393"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of prinplup?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of prinplup is 394"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of empoleon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of empoleon is 395"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of starly?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of starly is 396"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of staravia?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of staravia is 397"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of staraptor?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of staraptor is 398"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of bidoof?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of bidoof is 399"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of bibarel?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of bibarel is 400"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of kricketot?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of kricketot is 401"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of kricketune?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of kricketune is 402"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of shinx?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of shinx is 403"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of luxio?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of luxio is 404"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of luxray?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of luxray is 405"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of budew?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of budew is 406"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of roserade?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of roserade is 407"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of cranidos?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of cranidos is 408"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of rampardos?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of rampardos is 409"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of shieldon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of shieldon is 410"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of bastiodon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of bastiodon is 411"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of burmy?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of burmy is 412"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of wormadam-plant?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of wormadam-plant is 413"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mothim?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mothim is 414"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of combee?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of combee is 415"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of vespiquen?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of vespiquen is 416"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of pachirisu?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of pachirisu is 417"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of buizel?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of buizel is 418"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of floatzel?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of floatzel is 419"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of cherubi?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of cherubi is 420"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of cherrim?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of cherrim is 421"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of shellos?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of shellos is 422"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gastrodon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gastrodon is 423"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of ambipom?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of ambipom is 424"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of drifloon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of drifloon is 425"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of drifblim?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of drifblim is 426"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of buneary?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of buneary is 427"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lopunny?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lopunny is 428"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mismagius?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mismagius is 429"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of honchkrow?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of honchkrow is 430"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of glameow?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of glameow is 431"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of purugly?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of purugly is 432"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of chingling?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of chingling is 433"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of stunky?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of stunky is 434"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of skuntank?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of skuntank is 435"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of bronzor?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of bronzor is 436"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of bronzong?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of bronzong is 437"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of bonsly?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of bonsly is 438"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mime-jr?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mime-jr is 439"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of happiny?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of happiny is 440"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of chatot?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of chatot is 441"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of spiritomb?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of spiritomb is 442"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gible?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gible is 443"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gabite?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gabite is 444"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of garchomp?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of garchomp is 445"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of munchlax?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of munchlax is 446"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of riolu?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of riolu is 447"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lucario?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lucario is 448"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of hippopotas?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of hippopotas is 449"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of hippowdon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of hippowdon is 450"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of skorupi?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of skorupi is 451"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of drapion?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of drapion is 452"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of croagunk?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of croagunk is 453"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of toxicroak?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of toxicroak is 454"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of carnivine?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of carnivine is 455"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of finneon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of finneon is 456"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lumineon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lumineon is 457"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mantyke?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mantyke is 458"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of snover?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of snover is 459"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of abomasnow?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of abomasnow is 460"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of weavile?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of weavile is 461"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of magnezone?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of magnezone is 462"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of lickilicky?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of lickilicky is 463"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of rhyperior?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of rhyperior is 464"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of tangrowth?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of tangrowth is 465"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of electivire?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of electivire is 466"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of magmortar?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of magmortar is 467"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of togekiss?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of togekiss is 468"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of yanmega?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of yanmega is 469"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of leafeon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of leafeon is 470"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of glaceon?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of glaceon is 471"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gliscor?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gliscor is 472"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mamoswine?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mamoswine is 473"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of porygon-z?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of porygon-z is 474"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of gallade?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of gallade is 475"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of probopass?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of probopass is 476"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of dusknoir?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of dusknoir is 477"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of froslass?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of froslass is 478"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of rotom?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of rotom is 479"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of uxie?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of uxie is 480"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of mesprit?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of mesprit is 481"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of azelf?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of azelf is 482"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of dialga?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of dialga is 483"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of palkia?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of palkia is 484"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of heatran?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of heatran is 485"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of regigigas?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of regigigas is 486"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of giratina-altered?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of giratina-altered is 487"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of cresselia?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of cresselia is 488"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of phione?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of phione is 489"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of manaphy?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of manaphy is 490"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of darkrai?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of darkrai is 491"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of shaymin-land?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of shaymin-land is 492"
  },
  {
    "prompt": "What is the number of arceus?",
    "answer": "The number in the pokedex of arceus is 493"
  }
]

